e46fanatics.com 2016-05-07

# E46Fanatics.com Privacy Policy

This website is owned and operated by performanceIX, Inc. performanceIX values your right to privacy. This Privacy Policy is effective March 22, 2016 and describes the types of information that performanceIX gathers from visitors and how that information is used. performanceIX reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. The currently operative Privacy Policy will always be available by clicking on the Privacy Policy link on the home page. Please read this policy carefully and, if you have any questions, please email us at [pix@performanceix.com](mailto:pix@performanceix.com). 

We do not collect any personally identifiable information unless you specifically provide it to us. You may provide such information to us by registering on the Site or by otherwise specifically providing such information to us. 

_Unregistered Users_

We collect certain information necessary to assist us in operating the Site. We log your IP address to assist us in diagnosing server problems, administering our website, and tracking usage statistics. Your IP address is provided to you by your Internet Service Provider and may be constant or may be different each time you access the Internet, depending on the type of Internet service you have. We do not try to identify you through your IP address and it would be extremely difficult for us to do so. 

If you click through to the Site from another website, then we collect that information. This helps us learn where our visitors are coming from and helps us make the Site better. Any such information is collected and used only in the aggregate and although we can generate reports to help us understand the information as a whole, we cannot generate reports about specific users. If you have provided personal information to another website from which you click through to the Site, then you should review the privacy policy of that website to determine what information that website collects and how it is used. At present, the Site does not receive any personal information you may have provided to any website not operated by performanceIX and we have no plans to do so. If our plans should change, we will modify this Privacy Policy to reflect that change before any change is implemented, and any such personal information would be subject to this Privacy Policy. 

We may place small files known as “cookies” on your computer’s hard drive to help us learn about how visitors use our website and to provide our users with a better experience. A cookie may, for example, contain certain information that allows us to track your path through the Site, to determine whether you are a return visitor, and to automatically log you in to our Interactive Areas. Cookies do not permit us to personally identify you and cannot access any other data on your computer. Your web browser may provide a way for you to refuse cookies and you are free to do so without affecting your ability to access the Site. However, you will lose the ability to personalize your experience on the Site, including the ability to participate in any of our Interactive Areas. Cookies are harmless, so we encourage you to allow us to place one on your computer so that you can take full advantage of everything the Site has to offer. 

_Registered Users_

The above information concerning Unregistered Users also applies to Registered Users. Registration is voluntary, and has many benefits, including the ability to post messages and other information in our Interactive Areas, the ability to personalize the website to best serve your needs, and automatic registration with other car enthusiast websites we operate so that you can easily participate in the forums that interest you most. If you choose to register, then you will provide certain information to us, including a username, email address, location, and information about your car. That information may or may not include personally-identifiable information. 

_How We Use Your Information_

We use the information that we collect about you or that you provide to us for various purposes, including: registration and management of your account, to communicate with you, to enable us to publish forum posts that you write, to respond to your questions, to improve our products and services, to customize your experience of the website, to solicit information from you, to resolve disputes or problems, to prevent prohibited or illegal activities, and to otherwise enforce our Terms of Use. When you provide an e-mail address to us, we will use that to communicate with you. You can opt-out of receiving these emails if you wish by updating your personal preferences and unchecking the “receive email” box. 

_Disclosure of Personal Information_

We do not disclose your personal information to any third party, except as may be required by law. We do not sell or rent any personally identifiable information to any third party. We may share personally identifiable information with third-parties that we specifically engage to provide services to performanceIX such as market research, marketing services, and advertising agencies, but in those circumstances we will require those parties to use that information solely for the purpose of providing those services to performanceIX. We also may share personal information within the performanceIX family of websites. 

performanceIX must cooperate with legal authorities, and may be required to disclose personally identifiable information in response to requests from law enforcement authorities, or in response to a subpoena or other legal process. In the unlikely event that this should happen, we will provide only the information we must provide. We may also disclose personally identifiable information if we believe we must in order to prevent a violation of the law. By using the Site and by providing personally identifiable information to us, you consent to our doing so, in our sole discretion. You also agree that we may disclose personally identifiable information in the course of legal proceedings, if we reasonably believe that doing so might mitigate our liability or assist us in enforcing our legal rights. We also may share your information in connection with a corporate transaction, such as a divestiture, merger, consolidation, or asset sale, and in the unlikely event of bankruptcy. 

_Collection of Personally Identifiable Information by Third-Party Sites_

The Site may contain links to web sites of third parties. When you leave our website for a third-party website, we do not send any personally identifiable information to that website. However, we have no control over any third-party website or over any personally identifiable information that any third-party website may collect from you. Before providing any personally identifiable information to any such third-party website, you should review that website’s terms of use and privacy policy and make sure that they are acceptable to you. 

_E-Mail Opt-in and Opt-out_

If you provide your e-mail address to us, then you consent to our use of that e-mail address to contact you. We do not sell your e-mail address. If you wish to receive communications from us, then you may visit <http://forum.e46fanatics.com/profile.php?do=editoptions> and check the boxes in the “Receive E-mail” section. Once you have set your preferences, scroll to the bottom of the page and click on “Save Changes” to confirm your changes. If you later decide that you no longer wish to receive communications from us, simply go to that link and un-check the boxes again. Don’t forget to click on “Save Changes” to confirm. 

_How to review and update your personal information._

You can review and update the personal information you have provided through the registration process by visiting <http://forum.e46fanatics.com/profile.php?do=editprofile>

_How we protect your personal information._

performanceIX takes reasonable steps and complies with all applicable laws to protect your personally identifiable information. However, it is possible that third parties may unlawfully intercept transmissions of personal information, or otherwise access that information. In the unlikely event that someone should gain access to personally identifiable information, performanceIX will comply with any applicable laws on the notification of persons affected by the disclosure of personally identifiable information. 

_Children’s Privacy_

This website is a general audience site, and we do not knowingly collect information about children. Should a child whom we know to be under 13 send personal information to us, we will delete or destroy that information as soon as reasonably possible. 

_Use of our Websites from Outside the United States_

If you access our websites from outside the United States, you should know that your information may be transferred, stored, and processed in the United States. The applicable data protection and privacy laws of the United States may differ from those in your country. 

_How to Contact Us_

If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, you may contact us by clicking <http://forum.e46fanatics.com/sendmessage.php>

_Changes to this Privacy Policy._

We reserve the right to change this policy. The most recent version of this policy will always be posted here. You should review the policy periodically to make sure that you still agree to it and to make any desired changes to the personal information you have provided.
